{
    "questions": [{
            "problem": "Simplify: a + 4b + 9 + 6a + 2a",

            "choice1": "8a+4b+9",
            "choice2": "9a+4b+9",
            "choice3": "22ab",
            "choice4": "9a+17b",
            "correctanswer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 3z + 4x + 2z+ 4y + 5x",

            "choice1": "5z+4y+9x",
            "choice2": "9x+5y+5z",
            "choice3": "18xyz",
            "choice4": "4y+10x+5z",
            "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 4h + a + 5g+ g",

            "choice1": "4h+a+6g",
            "choice2": "a+7g+4h",
            "choice3": "6g+4h",
            "choice4": "4h+8g+a",
            "correctanswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": " Simplify: 2y + 9x + 3 + 4x + 7",

            "choice1": "13x+3y+10",
            "choice2": "2y+13x+10",
            "choice3": "14x+2y+10",
            "choice4": "10+12x+2y",
            "correctanswer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Evaluate 4a + 3b + 20 if a = 2 and b = 3",

            "choice1": "95",
            "choice2": "37",
            "choice3": "24",
            "choice4": "32",
            "correctanswer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Evaluate 8x + 2y if x = 6 and y = 5",

            "choice1": "60",
            "choice2": "11",
            "choice3": "58",
            "choice4": "50",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 3x + 2y + 4 + 9y",

            "choice1": "12y+3x+4",
            "choice2": "3x+11y+4",
            "choice3": "4+3x+14y",
            "choice4": "14xy+4",
            "correctanswer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 9 + 8x + 3y + 3 + 5y",

            "choice1": "8y+7x+12",
            "choice2": "13+8x+8y",
            "choice3": "8x+8y+12",
            "choice4": "12+8y",
            "correctanswer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 3x + 8 + 4y + 7 + 3x",

            "choice1": "4y+9x+56",
            "choice2": "9x+4y+56",
            "choice3": "4y+6x+16",
            "choice4": "6x+4y+15",
            "correctanswer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Simplify: 6x + 2y + 5y + 7 + y",

            "choice1": "7+x+8y",
            "choice2": "8y+7x+7",
            "choice3": "14xy+7",
            "choice4": "6x+8y+7",
            "correctanswer": "4"
        }
    ]
}